Hello, I am Savita Maiti,
an advisor [ __ ] product
holder of ICC Prudential Life Insurance Company. Today I will discuss a beautiful plan in front of you
called
Protect and Gain
Life. This is a combo plan because this
plan is made by combining IPS and Signature.
Through this plan, I will be profitable for myself and I will also be
able to provide protection to my family. This plan can be taken by any person between the ages of 18 and 50.
ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance Company thinks about everyone,
so this plan has been brought by thinking about everyone.
Currently, to take this plan,
no ITR file is required. If you have an income of 3 lakhs,
then yes, you must be a graduate. The
PPT of this plan i.e. the
premium paying term is five to 12,
i.e. someone can pay for five years,
someone can pay for six years, like this, up to 12 years
and their coverage can be kept at 60 or more.
Currently, I am trying to explain this plan with an example.
Let's say a
person who
takes 10 PPT, that is, he thinks
that he will pay the premium for 10 years and
keep this coverage till the age of 60. If he takes 10 PPT, then
his per year premium will be
taka. Then he will pay 10 years, that is, in 10
years, he will
pay a total of 5 lakh
taka. In return,
what he will get at the age of 60 is
46 lakh
taka. If he is alive, he will get this money
and if for some reason
he dies unfortunately,
then the
family will get coverage of 50 lakh
taka. And if there is an accidental death,
then the
family will get one crore taka. And if for some
reason he becomes accidentally disabled, that is, it is
found that due to some accident,
he has lost both eyes or has lost both
hands or legs, he cannot climb stairs, that
is, he has lost his ability to work,
in that case,
that person will get 50 lakh taka while he is alive.
This was the plan
where the family  Protection can be given, if you
survive, you can be profitable,
so
considering the current society, where accidents are increasing day by day, no
one is secure, if we
leave the house, we will definitely be able to
return home because accidents never
come, no one can say when and how they come,
so this plan is a suitable
plan for the present. We who love our family will
definitely take this plan and
we will definitely
tell our relatives and relatives who are well-wishers about this plan so that
they also take this plan and
they are aware of such plans. It is such a
beautiful plan,
so I would say that everyone needs to take this plan.
Thank you so much for today.